

STEFANIE ZWICKY

JUNIOR UX / UI

I am a communicative team player, enjoy learning new things and appreciate working with different people. As a service-oriented account manager, my previous focus has been on customer service and campaign management. With training as a UX/UI designer, I have further developed my skills in creative ideation to organizational planning and implementation and discovered my passion for creating new experiences for users and designing intuitive interfaces that make life better.

SKILLS

- Project Management & Customer
 Consulting
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- User Personas
- Research: Competitor & User
- Information Architecture
- Usability Testing
- Designing Online Marketing Ads
- Copywriting
- PR and Social Media
- Curiosity
- Communication

ICT

- Microsoft Office very good skills
- Social Media very good skills
- Figma good skills
- Adobe XD good skills
- WIX good skills
- Wordpress good skills
- Xandr good skills
- Adobe Illustrator basic knowledge
- Adobe InDesign basic knowledge
- Adobe Photoshop basic knowledge

EXPERIENCE

SOON WITH YOU?

UX/UI INTERN

Bank Vontobel / Zurich / September 2021 - February 2022

Internship at Bank Vontobel within the UX department. My activities:

- Design Pattern Library migration and maintenance
- Working on ongoing app development (designing wireframes, user testing, prototyping)
- Working on website relaunch: designing wireframes, usability testing
- Project lead in introducing Figma: creating training material, blogpost, training sessions

UX/UI DESIGNER TRAINEE

CareerFoundry / Berlin / October 2020 – September 2021

Intensive project-based training program for UX Designers, specializing in UX process and methodology that includes user research, user journeys, user personas, testing, information architecture, and visual design fundamentals.

 Designed 2 apps, both native mobile and mobile-first web application, using Figma for wireframes and prototypes.

ACCOUNT MANAGER

Matto-Group / Zurich / February 2019 – August 2020

Matto-Group is a start-up agency for media marketing with focus on buying and selling advertising space (online/offline) in the media industry.

- My activities:
 - Event marketing: Co-developing ideas for event presences of various large companies in the fields of telecommunication and insurance at Züri Fäscht
 - Media consulting and sales: Consulting and sales of online advertising spaces (display and programmatic) as well as coordination of campaign management including final reporting for clients from the media, retail, cosmetics, automotive, banking sectors
 - Copywriting: Creation of online advertising banners, content for the Matto-Group website and sales presentations, various PR reports, including an article on sponsoring Züri Fäscht
 - Strategic consulting: co-developing the strategy for new online advertising space for a cooking magazine
 - Influencer marketing: project briefing and consulting

TRAINEE SPONSORING / PR / MARKETING

Matto-Group / Zurich / February 2018 – January 2019

During my one-year traineeship, I gained experience in the areas of sponsoring (events), PR and marketing.

LANGUAGES

- German Native Language
- Englisch C1 level
 Cambridge CAE
- French B1 level
- Spanish basic knowledge
- Chinese basic knowledge

HOBBIES

- English Literature
- Horseback riding
- Art & Design
- Crocheting

REFERENCES

Will be gladly disclosed upon request during a personal meeting.

EDUCATION

• Bachelor of Arts in Sozialwissenschaften

Hauptfach: Publizistik- und Kommunikationswissenschaft Nebenfach: Englische Sprach- und Literaturwissenschaft

Universität Zürich 08.2014 – 07.2017

UX/UI Design course

CareerFoundry, Berlin 10.2020 – 09.2021

• SEA, Programmatic Advertising, Videomarketing & Crossmedia

Fachhochschule Nordwestschweiz

04.2020

• Introduction Programmatic Advertising Tool Xandr

Xandr, Zurich

04.2020

Basics in SEA und SEO

Google, Zurich 06./07.2019

• Basics in InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop and Acrobat DC

Digicomp Academy AG, Zurich

01.2018

• Adobe Photoshop CC Module I – Basics

Digicomp Academy AG, Zurich

12.2017